Tesla B-ORG
builds O
vehicles O
in O
California B-LOC

Alice B-PER
works O
at O
OpenAI B-ORG

Seattle B-LOC
hosts O
AI B-MISC
events O

Bob B-PER
uses O
PyTorch B-MISC
